(AUDIENCE CHEERING AND APPLAUDING FAINTLY)
四骑士！四骑士！
AUDIENCE: (CHANTING)
Horsemen! Horsemen!
四骑士！四骑士！
四骑士！四骑士！四骑士！四骑士！
Horsemen! Horsemen!Horsemen! Horsemen!
阿特拉斯: 以为我们弃场了？
ATLAS: Did you think we abandoned you?
(AUDIENCE CHEERING LOUDLY)
还是魔术技穷了？
Or that we'd run out of magic?
好好想想，女士先生们
Well, think again,
ladies and gentlemen,
准备好大开眼界吧
because you are
about to be amazed.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING LOUDLY)
既然各位在场 说明你们已经
If you're here right now,
then you have
循踪破译，解开了谜题
followed the clues
and cracked the code.
恭喜，欢迎入局
Congratulations, and welcome.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
阔别十年后 四骑士现在
It's been 10 years since
the horseman last appeared,
正式回归！
but we are back!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING LOUDLY)
好了，凑近点，再近点
Okay, so, come in close.
Mm, closer.
因为你自以为看清的越多
Because the more
you think you see,
就越容易被旧瓶装新酒的把戏
the easier it will be
to dress up old tricks
蒙骗过去
and fool you that they are new.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING LOUDLY)
我是 J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
So, my name is J. Daniel Atlas,
容我代表这几位魅力稍逊的同僚
and allow me
to speak as I often do
说一句……
for my less charismatic
colleagues when I say...
呼！回归的感觉真好！
Whoo! It is very good
to be back!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING LOUDLY)
没错，我们要么隐匿一阵
Yes. Yes.
We vanished for a while,
但在魔法界
but in the world of magic,
凡消失者，必重现
everything that disappears,
reappears.
只要戏法玩得对
Well, at least
if the trick is done right.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
我是梅里特·麦金尼
I'm Merritt McKinney. (CHUCKLES)
不像我的好哥们丹尼那么自恋
Unlike my, uh, very good
buddy here, Danny,
今晚入场的各位都挺谦虚
most of you checked your egos
at the door tonight.
你们摸进这场地下盛会
You found this
little underground soiree
就是想来“受骗”的
because you wanted
to get fooled.
大家好，我是杰克·怀尔德
Hey, everyone. I'm Jack Wilder.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING
AND SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
战争、瘟疫、气候剧变、AI
Wars, pandemics,
climate change, AI.
承认吧，此刻我们更需要魔法
Let's face it, we all need
magic more than ever.
所以请睁大眼睛
So I want you to pay
very close attention.
接下来的戏法不容错过
You are not gonna want
to miss this next trick.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
亨利·里维斯，现在冠了夫姓
Henley Reeves,
now Henley Reeves Stanley.
三娃两狗，硕士在手
Three kids, two dogs
and a master's degree.
久违了
It's been a while.
想我们吗？
Did you miss us?
(AUDIENCE CHEERING LOUDLY)
他们当年确实挺牛
Those guys were great
back in the day.
我以前也想当魔术师
I used to want to be a magician.
直到我过了中二年纪
- And then I turned 12.
- (BOTH LAUGH)
小心点，隔墙有耳
Careful,
they might be listening.
哎哟，我吓得直发抖呢
Ooh, I'm shaking
in my AllSaints.
他们能拿我怎样？
What are they gonna do?
(CHUCKLES)
金表是真的？
Is that real gold?
- 啥？
- 金表是真的吗？
- What?
- Is that real gold?
那当然，爷有钱
- Yeah, I'm rich.
- (SNORTS)
这可是魔术秀，哥们
This is a magic show, dude.
这的人不是扒手
Every fool here is a pickpocket,
就是肥羊
or a pickpocket's fool.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
- 刚那是俳句吗？
- 什么鬼？
- Was that a haiku?
- What was that?
各位手里都有一张牌
Each of you
just received a playing card.
不介意的话，请亮出来？
If you wouldn't mind, uh,
pulling it out?
好，现在来大洗牌
Right. Now, we're gonna
shuffle the deck,
随便找个身边人
so everybody find
a random person near them
跟他交换卡牌
and switch cards with them.
换完之后
And then when you've done that,
再找别人换一次
find somebody else
and switch with them.
好的，现在……
Okay, great. Uh, now...
那个谁，就是你
Uh, duh-duh-duh-duh-duh...
You there, down there.
- 我？
- 对，你的牌是？
- Me?
- Yeah. What is your card?
- 方片A
- 方片A，行
- Ace of diamonds.
- Ace of diamonds. Okay.
那让事情复杂点
Let's make things a little
more complicated here.
这里还有谁拿的是方片 A？
Does anybody else here
have the ace of diamonds?
等等，是我，方片 A！
Wait, it's me. Ace of diamonds!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
梅里特: 哟！
MERRITT: Ooh!
看来除了露拉，还有第五位骑士
Looks like we have a Fifth
Horseman not named Lula.
上台来吧，你是助手了
Come up on stage,
you're gonna be our helper.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
-搞起！
-上啊！
MAN 1: Do it! MAN 2: Yeah, go!
现在，看着我的眼睛
Now, uh, look into my eyes
然后……睡吧
and... sleep. (SNAPS FINGERS)
宝刀未老
- (AUDIENCE GASPS)
- (CHUCKLES) Still got it.
这孩子看着普通
Now, this might look like
an ordinary kid to you,
但今晚，他将如鬼神附体般
but tonight, he is going
to do extraordinary magic
施展魔法
like a man possessed.
字面意思的“附体”
- Literally.
- (AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
- 亨利
- 在
- Henley.
- Yes, Merritt.
麻烦你进到他身体里去
Would you mind
stepping inside his body?
- (SNAPS FINGERS)
- (AUDIENCE GASPS)
成了。杰克
Yep. And, Jack, uh,
你也把自己扔进去吧
why don't you throw yourself
on in there, too?
这我拿手
- What I do best.
- (SNAPS FINGERS)
上帝保佑你
- (AUDIENCE GASPS)
- And... Oh, God help you.
阿特拉斯，你也进去吧
Atlas, why don't you
slither on inside, as well?
- (SNAPS FINGERS)
- (AUDIENCE GASPS)
我只好也挤进去了
And I might as well
wedge myself in there, too.
人多力量大 方能创奇迹
It takes a village to make magic.
- (SNAPS FINGERS)
- (AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
MAN IN AUDIENCE: Oh!
WOMAN: Whoa!
J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯在此
(AS ATLAS)
J. Daniel Atlas in the house.
想看魔术吗？
So, who wants
to see a magic trick?
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
交给你了，梅里特
Take it away, Merritt.
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
哈啰，帅哥美女们
(AS MERRITT)
Hello, you beautiful people.
众所周知梅里特·麦金尼会读心术
Now, everyone knows that
Merritt McKinney reads minds.
现在，我是他 还是他是谁？天晓得
Well, now, I'm him.
Or he's me. Who knows?
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
呃，我感觉到今晚有人
Uh, I'm sensing
someone came here tonight
不是来享受魔法的 而是来拆台的
not to enjoy magic,
but to tear it down.
布雷特·菲尼根在场吗？
Is there a Brett Finnegan
in the house?
布雷特: 干嘛？
- BRETT: What up?
- (AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(BRETT'S FRIEND
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
你和你的狐朋狗友
Now, you and your friends here
搞了个“霍巴特营加密交易所”
set up the
Camp Hobart Crypto Exchange.
- 没错，咋地？
- 就这业务
- Fact. Yep. Yeah.
- It's what we're about.
卷走了纽约市民
Took the good people
of New York's
一半的养老福利金
employee pension and
welfare fund half its cash.
呃，那是四舍五入夸大了
- (AUDIENCE BOOING)
- Uh, you're rounding up,
而且风险提示写得很清楚
and also, the risks were
laid out very clearly.
愿者上钩嘛，老兄
Everybody knew what
they were getting into, dude.
那你有没有把利润藏到海外？
Did you hide
the profits offshore?
尾号为
Account ending
53297 的帐户？
in 53297?
(紧张笑)
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
你不可能知道
除非你有我的……
You couldn't know that
without my, uh...
(观众惊呼)
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
(杰克的声音) 哟，金表是真的？
(AS JACK) Oh, is this real gold?
(观众欢呼)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
布雷特，看好你的东西啊
Brett, you ought
to be more careful
老兄
with your things, man.
梅里特会读心
但我杰克嘛
Merritt's a psychic,
but me, Jack,
手快
I'm into sleight of hand.
- (观众惊叹)
- 问问你朋友
- (AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS)
- Ask your friends.
他们刚为缩小贫富差距做了贡献
They've just done their part
to close the wealth gap.
- (观众欢呼)
- 什么？搞什么……
- (AUDIENCE CHEERING)
- What? What the...
来，这就叫“再分配”
Now, here's
a little redistribution.
喂！喂！
Hey! Hey, hey!
(观众欢呼)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
谢谢，谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
等著收律师函吧！
我要揍死你！
Lawyer up, dude!
I'll kick your ass!
(亨利的声音) 噢噢！
(AS HENLEY) Uh-oh!
有人忘了亨利会飞哦
Someone forgot Henley can fly.
(观众欢呼)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
接下来交给我们
但请给台上这位
We can take it from here,
but a round of applause
最棒的骑士一点掌声
for the best Horseman on stage.
呼！哇哦
Whoo! Wow.
布雷特: 喂喂喂，行行行
BRETT: Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey.
真精彩。各位，举起酒杯
Fantastic. So, everybody,
I want you to take your drink,
把酒倒在你们的牌面上
and I want you to pour it
onto the face of your card.
倒吧
Can you do that?
杰克: 每张牌显现出的
12 个独特单词
JACK: Those 12 unique words
on each of your cards
就是新加密钱包的密码
form the password
to your new crypto wallet.
- 男观众: 噢！
- 亨利: 登上去
- MAN IN AUDIENCE: Oh!
- HENLEY: Log on
你们会发现布雷特偷的几百万
and you'll find Brett's
stolen millions more...
已公平退还
fairly redistributed.
天啊，五……
五万块！
Oh, my God. Fifty...
50,000 bucks!
五万！
50,000!
(观众大声欢呼)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING LOUDLY)
你死定了，混蛋！
You're freaking done, dude!
喔喔！消消气，小姜饼
Whoa, whoa!
Cool your head, gingerbread,
我预见到了一个画面
'cause I am having a vision.
条子马上要破门而入了！
Eh, maybe cops are gonna come
bursting through that door!
所以你也变个魔术吧
So perform a magic trick
of your own
赶紧消失
三、二、一
and disappear
in three, two, one.
(观众喧闹)
(AUDIENCE CLAMORING)
(警笛长鸣)
(SIREN WAILING)
阿特拉斯 (录音):
好了，凑近点，再近点
ATLAS: (ON RECORDING)
Now come in close. Mm, closer.
因为你自以为看清的越多
就越容易被……
Because the more you think
you see, the easier it will be
- 旧瓶装新酒的把戏……
- 什么？
- to dress up old tricks...
- What?
蒙骗过去
and fool you
that they are new.
(倒吸凉气)
(GASPS)
天啊，不
Oh, my God, no.
不！
No!
(啜泣) 不！
(SOBBING) No!
(击打床单)
(HITS SHEET)
(戏剧性音乐)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(警笛长鸣)
(SIREN WAILING)
我觉得吧，你干得不错
Look, in my opinion,
I think you did a great job.
我扮的阿特拉斯挺好
Uh, I think my Atlas was good.
但梅里特还得练练
My Merritt could
probably use some work.
- 琼: 嗯
- 听著像个圣地牙哥的大烟鬼
- JUNE: Mm.
- It's like a San Diego stoner
和捕虾船长的串儿
and a shrimp boat captain
had a baby.
- 是是
- (轻笑)
- Sure.
- (CHUCKLING)
琼: 说真的，博斯科
你怎么做到的？
JUNE: No, seriously, Bosco,
I don't know how you do it.
模仿秀不仅要声音像
A good impersonation
isn't just about the mimicry.
还得抓细节
It's about attention to detail,
个性、神韵
personality and nuance.
行行行，我试试
Okay. Okay.
Let me try, let me try.
呃…… (尖嗓子)
我是 J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
Um... (HIGH-PITCHED)
I'm J. Daniel Atlas.
(喷口水) 离得越近，看得越瞎
(SPUTTERS) The closer
you look, the less you see.
查理: (笑) 有内味了
CHARLIE: (LAUGHS)
It was something.
嗯，再练练吧
Yep. Uh, you'll work on it.
- 我刚那下不赖
- 是个好开头
- I wasn't bad.
- It was a good start.
- 但还得打磨
- 行吧
- But it could use some work.
- Okay, sure.
- 你老盯着啥呢？
- 没事，没啥
- What do you keep looking at?
- Nothing, nothing, nothing.
哥们，振作点
看看我们，多风光！
Dude, cheer up.
Guys, come on! Look at us!
看看我们走了多远
今晚简直赚翻了
Look at how far we've come.
We totally scored tonight.
琼: 好吧，下次
你戴那顶粉色假发，行吗？
JUNE: All right, next time,
you wear the pink wig, okay?
博斯科: 不行
BOSCO: No.
- 伙计，又锁上了
- 行，我来撬
- Dude, it's locked again.
- Okay, I'll pick it.
等等，别急
来那一招
Wait, wait, wait, hold on.
Do the thing.
- 不要
- 求你了，来那一招
- No.
- Please do the thing.
- 没必要吧
- 超帅的
- It's so unnecessary.
- It's so cool.
- 我帮你拿包
- 真没必要
- I'll hold your bag.
- It's so unnecessary.
- 来嘛，多好玩
- 好吧
- Come on, it's fun.
- Okay.
(悬疑音乐)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
博斯科: 你行的
BOSCO: You got this.
(哼声)
(GRUNTS)
- 她就像个小马里奥
- 确实像马里奥
- She's like a little Mario.
- She is like Mario.
查理: 小心，小心
博斯科: 求你别死
CHARLIE: Careful, careful.
BOSCO: Please don't die.
博斯科: 没事吧？ 琼: 没事
BOSCO: Are you okay? JUNE: Yeah.
博斯科: 我要是有这身手
我就天天翻墙
BOSCO: If I could do that,
I would only do that.
- (轻笑) 太酷了
- 简直疯了
- (CHUCKLES) It's so cool.
- It's insane.
开心了？
Happy?
- 嗯，太棒了
- 是啊
- Yeah, that was awesome.
- Yeah.
快放我们进去，好冷
Please let us in. It's cold.
- 琼: 呼
- (铁门响动)
- JUNE: Whoo.
- (GATE RATTLING)
全城最好的公寓
Best apartment
in the whole city.
没错，除了我们也
没人能看到了
Yep, and no one
will ever see it but us.
(琼轻笑)
(JUNE CHUCKLES)
(背景音乐微弱播放)
(CRUSADES BY GEESE
PLAYING FAINTLY)
♪ 每个人…… ♪
♪ Everybody... ♪
真可惜
It's such a shame.
♪ 但身披铠甲
我是硬汉…… ♪
♪ But in my armor
I am a man... ♪
阿特拉斯 (录音):
凑近点
ATLAS: (ON RECORDING)
Come in close.
再近点
Closer.
琼: 那家伙完蛋了
JUNE: That guy is so screwed.
(录音继续模糊播放)
(RECORDING CONTINUES
PLAYING INDISTINCTLY)
现在谁发财了？
Who's rich now?
查理，能把那玩意关了吗？
求你了
Charlie, can you turn
that thing off, please?
今晚我已经听够阿特拉斯了
I think I've had
enough Atlas for one night.
查理: 收到
CHARLIE: Yeah, I got you.
阿特拉斯: 消失者，必重现
ATLAS: disappears, reappears.
只要
戏法玩得对
At least
if the trick is done right.
博斯科，看看有披萨吗？
我饿死了
Bosco, can you check
for pizza? I'm so hungry.
博斯科: 唉，我也是
BOSCO: Ugh, me, too.
阿特拉斯 (录音):
我们是四骑士！
ATLAS: (ON RECORDING)
We are the Four Horsemen!
博斯科: 没披萨
但有啤酒
BOSCO: No pizza,
but we got beer.
- 而且，真的只有啤酒
- 再近点，因为
- And, no, literally just beer.
- Closer. Because
- 你自以为看清的越多……
- 博斯科: 谁要？
- the more you think you see...
- BOSCO: Any takers?
- 我要一瓶
- (悬疑音乐)
- Yeah, I'll have one.
- (INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
伙计，说真的
把那玩意关了
Dude, seriously,
turn that thing off.
我关了啊
I did.
行吧。真逗，各位
这边的投影仪在哪儿？
Okay. Real funny, guys.
Where's the other projector?
我不是全息影像
I'm not a hologram.
“我不是全息影像”
对，是是是
"I'm not a hologram."
Right. Yes.
全息影像
都会这么说
Exactly what
a hologram would say.
- 天啊，你是真人
- 别再摸我的脸
- Oh, my God, you're real.
- Never touch my face again.
抱歉抱歉。我以为
你是全息影像
I'm so sorry. I thought
that you were a hologram.
我不该那样的
我是你的超级粉丝
I would never do that.
I'm a huge fan of yours.
你好吗？ (喘气)
How are you? (PANTING)
你怎么找到我们的？
How did you find us?
不知道
我就花了大概 30 秒
I don't know.
Took me about 30 seconds.
既然我这么容易
就找到了你们
And if it was this easy
for me to find you,
警察找过来
又有多难呢？
how hard would it be
for the police?
- 哇，等等，警察？
- 阿特拉斯: 对，警察
- Whoa, hold on, the police?
- ATLAS: Yeah, the police.
警察为什么要找我们？
Why would the police
be looking for us?
呃，不知道
也许是因为
Uh, I don't know,
what about that
你们刚搞的那场抢劫？
little heist you just pulled?
或者因为你们
私闯民宅
Or the fact that you're
squatting in this place
又或者你们偷的电
or that your electricity
comes from
是从墙角电箱接出来的？
the circuit box in the corner?
谁知道呢，啥都有可能
我说的对吗，波波？
I don't know, it could be
anything. Am I right, Bozo?
(轻笑) 博斯科
(CHUCKLES) Bosco.
- 阿特拉斯: 嗯哼
- 博斯科·勒罗伊
- ATLAS: Hmm.
- Bosco Leroy.
啊，没错，对
博斯科·勒罗伊
Ah, that's right, yeah,
Bosco Leroy.
怎么，你是从 ChatGPT 上
What, did you type, uh,
搜了个“虚构魔术师名字”吗？
"fictional magician name"
into ChatGPT?
不，那是我的
真名，阿特拉斯
No, that's actually
my real name, Atlas.
阿特拉斯: 嗯哼
ATLAS: Hmm.
怎么，跟你妈
有一腿的是地图吗？
What, did your mom
have sex with a map?
(琼和查理大笑)
(JUNE AND CHARLIE LAUGH)
- 这一点也不好笑
- 阿特拉斯: 嗯哼
- That's not funny.
- ATLAS: Hmm.
你根本不了解我们，老兄
You don't know
anything about us, dude.
- 我了如指掌
- 噢
- I know everything about you.
- Oh.
名字可疑的博斯科·勒罗伊
The dubiously named Bosco Leroy,
大好的演艺前程
a promising acting career
被沉重的助学贷款给毁了
cut short
by crippling student loans.
从朱利亚德退学
是挺遗憾
It's a bummer you had to
drop out of Juilliard,
但你从未
停止表演
but you never
stopped performing.
呃，没记错的话
你上一份有薪工作
Uh, if memory serves,
your last paid gig,
是在时代广场扮艾摩吧？
I think, was dressing as Elmo
in Times Square?
首先，我没扮过艾摩
Okay, first of all,
I was never Elmo.
那是红色天线宝宝
It's the red Teletubby.
小波！
Po!
- 啥？
- 红色天线宝宝
- What?
- The red Teletubby.
- 她叫小波
- 哦，小波！
- Her name is Po.
- Oh, Po!
她是我的最爱
She's my favorite one.
- 查理: 是吧？
- (琼轻笑)
- CHARLIE: Right?
- (JUNE CHUCKLES)
- 她叫小波
- 琼: 可爱
- Her name is Po.
- JUNE: Cute.
还有你，琼·鲁克莱尔
And you, June Rouclere.
被爸妈强塞进的
Kicked out
of every boarding school
每所寄宿学校都开除了
your parents
forced you to attend.
我看你不太喜欢
服从权威啊
Not a big fan
of authority, I take it.
呃，让我猜猜
Uh, let me guess.
你觉得“老古董”们
搞坏了这地球
Uh, you think the "olds"
broke the planet
你们这一代
有责任来收拾烂摊子
and it's your generation's
duty to clean up their mess.
- 说对了吗？
- 说错了吗？
- Am I right?
- Am I wrong?
全中
No.
所以你离家出走
And so, you ran away from home,
一路到了纽约
在坦宁魔术店
made your way to New York,
where you ran into this guy
遇见了这家伙
查理·盖伊斯
at Tannin's Magic Shop,
Charlie Gayes.
- 对，嗨
- 嗨
- Yeah, hi.
网上关于你的资料不多
I actually couldn't find
a lot about you online.
但我知道你是孤儿
Although, I do know
you were an orphan and
童年一直在寄养家庭间
辗转流离
you were in and out of foster
care your entire childhood,
直到遇上这俩货
and that you didn't know
the meaning of family
你才懂了什么是家
until you hooked up
with these two.
于是你们三个这几年来
And so, the three of you
have been working
一直在演你们的
罗宾汉小把戏
your little Robin Hood act
for years now,
试图用一个个戏法
改变世界
trying to change the world
one trick at a time,
直到这回玩了把大的
也就是盗用我的身份
all leading to your riskiest
theft to date, my identity.
当时你在场？
You were there?
你们把我们的脸
You had our faces plastered
贴满了全城的脚手架和地铁站
on every scaffolding
and subway stop in the city.
顺便说一句，这侵权了
That's copyright infringement,
by the way.
我当然在场
Of course I was there.
觉得怎么样？
So, what'd you think?
我觉得你的梅里特还得练练
I think your Merritt needs work.
- 我就说吧
- 别提这茬
- I knew it.
- That's a sensitive topic.
- 你懂个屁
- 他在撒谎
- You don't even get it.
- No. He's lying.
但整体设计令人印象深刻
But overall design
was impressive.
我想你应该就是
那个闷葫芦吧？
And that's you, I assume,
the quiet guy?
- 典型的幕后推手
- 嗯，那个
- Textbook, behind the scenes.
- Yeah, well,
- 亚历山大·赫尔曼……
- 天啊
- Alexander Herrmann...
- Oh, boy.
他说过，真正设计魔术的人
he said that the people
who designed his tricks
才是真正的天才
were the real geniuses.
既然你知道他的大名
The fact that you know
that man's name,
显然你是“幕后”的
"behind the scenes" clearly.
而你，手法很高超
非常灵巧
And you, your sleight of hand
was advanced. Good dexterity.
身手敏捷
真的，我很佩服
You're quick and nimble on your
feet. Really, I was impressed.
- 谢谢
- 不客气
- Thanks.
- ATLAS: You're welcome.
听起来我们挺棒的
Sounds like we're pretty great.
差得远呢
ATLAS: You're far from it.
不过，稍微调教一下
也许能成
<font